I am not gonna fold.
(Raj:)Well, excuse me. I don't think
Penny's out of line. You don't own her.
It's like my girl Beyoncé says:
"If you like it,
you should've put a ring on it."
(Howard:)At the very least, when she found out
Leonard was upset about it...
(Howard:)-...she should've backed off.
-Like when a guy's upset...
...his friend agreed to take a class
with him and then doesn't...
(Raj:)...because he's doing a juice fast
with his mother?
(Howard:)I didn't know you were upset
about that.
Really? Did you miss the subtle indicators?
Like me saying, "Howard, I am upset."
HOWARD: Okay, sorry.
-Maybe it's different in this country.
(Raj:)Back in India, it means you're upset
with a guy named Howard.
(Howard:)-I said I'm sorry.
-Sorry doesn't make up for the fact...
(Raj:)...I had to make chicken and rice
with this vegan guy.
(Leonard:)Do you know
what vegan chicken and rice is? Rice.
You think I was having fun? Sitting
around listening to my mother say:
[AS MRS. WOLOWITZ] "Have you ever
peed so much in your life?"
(Raj:)Oh, my God.
You are such a mama's boy.
HOWARD: Don't bring my mother into this!
-You brought your mother into this!